[Music]
unlock your financial future with FWD
Insurance hi I am Karissa kulala your
financial wealth planner at FWD
Insurance why choose
FWD we the best life insurance in the
Philippines every agent agrees FWD is a
leader in providing top-notch
insurance without our health insurance
100% of your funds are returned at 75 if
not
claimed claim up to 3 million pesos if
diagnosed with critical illness 1
million per
claim you also get an additional 200k
benefit for minor critical
illnesses this plan protects your family
and covers hospital bills for your peace
of
mind choose flexible payment terms 5 10
or even 20 years tailored to your
needs enjoy discounts if you opt to pay
annually great savings
ahead if diagnosed with critical illness
you won't have to pay any future
premiums interested in learning more get
in touch with me
directly you can PM me on my Facebook
profile Isa
kulala or email me at fisak kulala
gmail.com to start your
journey let's secure your financial
future together with FWD
insurance contact me today and start
planning for a brighter tomorrow
[Music]